firsttennessee.com 2007-12-11

# First Tennessee | All Things Financial : Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment to Your Privacy

We value your relationship with us, and we know that respect for your privacy is the very foundation of that relationship. Since our company was founded in 1864, we have built a reputation based on trust. Advances in technology have made safeguarding private information all the more important. Along with our promise to provide you _All Things Financial®_ , we promise to safeguard the information you share with us.

## About this Privacy Notice

This notice answers some important questions about customer information. It describes our privacy policies including how we collect, use and safeguard customer information. It also explains how you can direct us not to share certain types of information within our family of companies.

## Who is Covered by this Notice?

This notice applies to all of our current and former customers. 

## What Kinds of Information Do We Collect?

We collect the following types of information about our customers:

  * Income, marital status, age, driver license and Social Security numbers and other information from applications and other forms you complete
  * Loan payment history, account balances and other information about transactions you conduct with us, our affiliates, or others
  * Account information from other companies that you ask us to maintain online for you
  * Credit scores or credit histories from credit reporting agencies and other information such as demographic information and insurance claims information we receive from third parties

We call all of this information "Customer Information."

## How Do We Use This Information to Your Benefit?

We use Customer Information to provide you with superior service and value, in other words, _All Things Financial®_. Sharing Customer Information can **save you time** because you're not continually supplying our affiliates with the same information. It can **reduce the amount of unwanted mail** you receive because we send you only information that may truly interest you. It also **allows you to get the assistance you need** through our telephone service centers.

## How Do We Protect Customer Information?

Our employees have limited access to Customer Information. They have access only when it will help you do business with us or help us do business with you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with government regulations to guard Customer Information.

## Do We Share Information with Outside Companies?

We do not sell Customer Information to outside companies to use for their own marketing purposes. Outside organizations that provide us services (such as printing or mailing) or help us provide you with products or services you request (such as clearing brokerage transactions or underwriting insurance applications) may receive Customer Information to help us provide you with these products and services. We may also provide Customer Information to companies that perform marketing services for us or to financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. These companies help us provide you with _All Things Financial®_ , and **they are obligated to keep Customer Information confidential**. We also share Customer Information with others when it is required or permitted by law, such as to credit bureaus or to comply with subpoenas and summonses.

## Do We Share Information Within Our Family of Companies?

Sharing Customer Information among the financial service providers in our family of companies is the key to providing you with _All Things Financial®_. We may share application or credit information about customers with our internal broker-dealers, insurance agents, mortgage company, or other affiliates because they may have products or services that could benefit you.

## Do You Have Any Choices to Make About Sharing Customer Information?

**If you do not want us to share application and credit information with another company in our family of companies, please call us** at (877) 242-9880. When you call, someone will be able to answer your questions about privacy, and, if you choose, you may request that we not share application or credit information within our family of companies. Please remember that if you ask that we not share Customer Information in this way, you may not receive information about our products or services that may interest you. **If you have already called us and requested that we not share this type of Customer Information, there is no need to make this request again.**

Please know that even if you do ask that we not share application or credit information about you with our affiliates, we are permitted by law to share transaction and experience information such as account balances and payment history within our family of companies.

If you have a joint account, we will treat a request not to share credit or application information by one account holder as applying only to that account holder unless the customer notifies us that he or she is acting on behalf of the other account holders. If your insurance policy names more than one person as the insured parties, we will treat a request not to share this type of information by one insured as applying only to that person unless he or she notifies us that he or she is acting on behalf of the other insured party. 

## What About Health Information?

We may collect personal health information, like medical reports, for certain products or services that we offer. We do not share personal health information with anyone except as may be requested or required in connection with processing a product or service you have requested or as required or permitted by law.

## What if Your Information is Not Correct?

We have procedures in place to maintain accurate Customer Information. These procedures include responding to requests to correct inaccurate Customer Information. If you believe our customer records contain incorrect information about you, call or write to us at the telephone number or address listed on your account statement.

## How Do We Keep You Up to Date on our Privacy Policies?

We will provide you with a privacy notice each year as long as you have a relationship with us. If we make material changes to our notice, we'll let you know. We'll also post our updated privacy notice on our Web sites, [www.firsttennessee.com](http://www.firsttennessee.com/), [www.firsthorizon.com](http://www.firsthorizon.com/) and [www.synaxisgroup.com](http://www.synaxisgroup.com/). If you open another account or obtain another product or service from another company within our family of companies, you may receive another copy of this privacy notice. Certain customers may receive a separate notice about specific privacy policies that may apply to their products or services. This privacy notice was last updated in March, 2004, and replaces any previous notices you may have received about the privacy policies for our family of companies.

## What If You Suspect Identity Theft?

If you're concerned that someone has unauthorized access to your personal information, please call us immediately at (800) 382-5465 so we can take steps to help protect you. You should also report your concerns to:

  * Your local law enforcement officials
  * The Federal Trade Commission identity theft hotline at 877-ID-Theft
  * The Social Security Administration Fraud Hotline at 800-269-0271
  * Your credit card companies. Remember, knowing where to find your credit card information and toll-free contact numbers will help in an emergency.
  * National credit reporting organizations that can place a fraud alert on your name and Social Security Number:

  * Equifax (800) 525-6285
  * Experian (888) 397-3742
  * Trans Union (800) 680-7289

## Which Companies Make Up Our Family of Companies?

Our privacy promise applies to information about current and former customers of the First Horizon, First Tennessee, and the Synaxis companies listed below -- and divisions of those companies. When the term "affiliate" or "family of companies" is used in this notice, it means those companies listed below **and** any other company owned or controlled by First Horizon National Corporation.

  * Employers Risk Services, Inc.
  * First Horizon*
  * First Horizon Bank*
  * First Horizon Equity LendingSM*
  * First Horizon Home Loans**
  * First Horizon Home Loan Corporation
  * First Horizon Insurance Services, Inc.
  * First Horizon Investment Services+
  * First Horizon Lending Center***
  * First Horizon Mint Distribution, Inc.
  * First Horizon MSAver Resources, Inc.
  * First Tennessee Bank National Association
  * First Tennessee Brokerage, Inc.
  * First Tennessee Insurance Services, Inc.
  * FT Insurance Corporation
  * FTN Financial Capital Markets*
  * FTN Financial Securities Corp.
  * FTN Midwest Research Securities Corp.
  * Highland Capital Management Corp.
  * Killebrew, Lyman & Woodworth x
  * Mann, Smith & Cummings, Inc.
  * First Horizon Insurance Agency, Inc.
  * Peoples Bank*
  * Polk & Sullivan Group, Inc.
  * SFSR, Inc.
  * Synaxis Benefits Services xx
  * Synaxis Group, Inc.

  * * A division of First Tennessee Bank National Association
  * \+ A division of First Tennessee Brokerage, Inc.
  * **First Horizon Home Loan Corporation doing business as First Horizon Home Loans
  * ***First Horizon Home Loan Corporation doing business as First Horizon Lending Center
  * xPolk & Sullivan Group, Inc. doing business as Killebrew, Lyman & Woodworth
  * xx Polk & Sullivan Group, Inc. doing business as Synaxis Benefits Services

## For California Residents Only

The rights you have under federal law are stated in our privacy notice you receive from us. As a California consumer, you have two (2) additional choices. You may restrict the sharing of information with our affiliates (companies we own or control) and with outside financial companies (companies we contract with to provide financial products and services to you). View more information.

## Our Web Linking Policy

Our Web site may contain links to content provided by third-party sources. First Horizon and its affiliates can not be held responsible for content found on any sites beyond our own.
